{
  "version": 2.0,
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the following Electronic array Geometry is used in this experiment?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Wenner Array",
        "b": "Pole-Dipole Array",
        "c": "Dipole-Dipole Array",
        "d": "Schlumberger Array"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "According to IS 15736:2007, what is the range of resistivity (in Ohm-m) for groundwater? ",
      "answers": {
        "a": "10-100",
        "b": "10-800",
        "c": "10-1000",
        "d": "10-8000"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "In the experiment, the inner electrodes are current electrodes and it causes the flow of current",
      "answers": {
        "a": "True",
        "b": "False"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "The apparent resistance depends on",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Potential drop",
        "b": "Flow of current",
        "c": "Distance between the electrodes",
        "d": "All of the above"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "The apparent resistivity measured in",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Ohm",
        "b": "Mho",
        "c": "Ohm-m",
        "d": "Siemen-m"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "c",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "In general, the depth of the soil sample is",
      "answers": {
        "a": "One-eight to the distance between current electrodes",
        "b": "One-sixth to the distance between current electrodes",
        "c": "One-fourth to the distance between current electrodes",
        "d": "One-third to the distance between current electrodes"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "d",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "The voltmeter is used for measuring the current",
      "answers": {
        "a": "True",
        "b": "False"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "The terminals P1 and P2 in the georesistivity meter are connected to",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Current Electrode",
        "b": "Potential Electrodes",
        "c": "Battery",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "The terminals C1 and C2 in the georesistivity meter are connected to",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Current Electrode",
        "b": "Potential Electrodes",
        "c": "Battery",
        "d": "None of the above"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "a",
      "difficulty": ""
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following instrument is NOT used in this test?",
      "answers": {
        "a": "Battery",
        "b": "Stopwatch",
        "c": "Hammer",
        "d": "Electrodes"
      },
      "explanations": {
        "a": "",
        "b": "",
        "c": "",
        "d": ""
      },
      "correctAnswer": "b",
      "difficulty": ""
    }
  ]
}
